[The Old Story of Yu Hong]
[Episode 11]
Aren't there peeled ones here?
You'll break your little teeth.
Is it tasty?
Yes.
Listen,
clear this table
and bring the food over here.
Eating here again?
The kid is watching TV.
Tasty, right?
Move aside.
Okay.
You're blocking his view of the TV.
Qiu, don't eat too many snacks.
-Or you won't want to have the meal later.
-Let him eat.
What's it to you?
Hurry up and clean up.
I'm back.
Your grandpa is back.
Grandpa.
On the road ahead,
another person got run over.
Man, it was brutal.
He was crushed flat.
Blood everywhere.
How many cars must have run over him?
I don't know.
They found over a dozen cars
with blood on their tires,
but they all said
they weren't the first to hit him.
It was dark.
They didn't see
someone was in the middle of the road.
So tragic.
So pitiful.
Give me the remote.
You got another bracelet?
You're always decked in gold and silver.
Are you worried others won't know
where our family's money comes from?
My son bought it for me.
Just show off.
Bring some water.
For a case like this,
what would the verdict be?
What else could it be?
No evidence.
Pay some money and that's it.
Why would anyone
run to the middle of the road
for no reason?
Probably he got drunk.
It's all because of alcohol.
Um, the Sun family next door
just had another chubby grandson.
Two now?
Look at them.
How do they have such good fortune?
A thriving family
with lots of children and grandchildren.
Look.
T-This.
Everything's so salty.
Th-These heavy dishes
are so greasy.
The TV says
stewed meat
has... what's it called?
Purines.
Right, purines.
We should eat less of it.
Make a fish
for our chubby grandson
to nourish his brain.
Nourish the brain, so he can be smarter.
Right.
No.
We can't hit him with a car.
I... I faint at the sight of blood.
A car accident has to involve a car.
What if there aren't enough cars
on the road?
How are we supposed to kill him?
The police will see right through it.
Then let's wait till he's drunk
and leave him in the middle of the road.
Like last time?
You dragged him back halfway there!
What if he doesn't get run over
and wakes up?
He'd wake up and find himself sleeping
in the middle of the road!
What would he think happened?
Then who would end up dead? Who?
These days,
his father keeps urging him
to chase down contracts every day.
He's out wining and dining every day.
We have plenty of chances.
Next time he goes out drinking,
we'll pick him up together.
We'll dump him
somewhere deserted along the way.
We'll hit him first.
Make sure he's dead.
Then we'll run him over.
Crush him to pieces.
Leave him there.
Then we leave and go to the hospital.
Later when cops ask,
tell them I had a stomachache halfway.
So he told you to take me to emergency.
And he walked home by himself.
There'll be doctors and nurses
to testify for us.
We definitely will be fine.
[Dragon Palace Seafood Restaurant]
Where are we going?
We had a great time... drinking.
Perfect.
Come on.
Book a room.
Why do I get the feeling
that you can hold your liquor better now?
You can drink a lot now.
-I think you really...
-Dewu.
You can drink a lot now.
Quit spinning around.
Who?
What's going on?
Bro, this is...
What's wrong with you?
Sorry, bro.
You...
Well, this...
Why are you here?
I was worried, so I came to take you home.
I was worried you'd drink too much.
Look at you.
I'm pestered by this old woman
every day!
I have no free time at all!
Mrs. Li?
Hello, bro.
Mrs. Li is so pretty.
You're a lucky guy.
-Thank you. Thank you.
-She was prettier when she was young.
I'm taking him home.
-Let's go.
-She's old now.
She's not pretty anymore.
-Let's go. The kid is at home.
-I'm not leaving.
I'm treating him to karaoke.
Mrs. Li is coming with us, right?
-No.
-Mr. Yang. Mr. Yang.
-Sorry.
-No. She's not coming.
I'm taking Mr. Li home.
I'm not leaving!
-I want to sing!
-Bye bye.
Go home and keep Mrs. Li company!
Save me a room!
You're staggering. Be careful!
Let's go sing.
Shasha Hair Salon.
Sing. Wash hair.
Sis, I'm not leaving!
Again!
Wash hair.
Let's go sing.
Dewu.
Pee.
Get off and pee.
Hurry, come on.
I didn't say I wanted to pee.
Yes, you did. You said you wanted to pee
as soon as you got in the car.
Come on.
Pee?
Dewu, let's go. Come on.
Not... Not here!
Don't, don't, don't!
You... You can't pee here!
It's dark here.
Um... you'll pee on yourself here.
Then where should I pee?
Up ahead. Up ahead.
Over there. There's a tree over there.
So fussy, old woman.
Why are you so fussy?
Let's go.
Every day,
why are you... why are you...
why are you always wasting money?
Let's go.
Every day, you...
So much trouble
every day!
Come.
Come, come.
Come. Hold on tight.
Pee.
Where should I pee?
Over here. Here. Here.
Here.
I'm going... going home!
-Get lost!
-Come on. Step back a bit.
Here. Here.
Here.
Unzip me!
Stand still.
Hurry up.
Okay, you can pee now.
Unzip me.
Where are you going?
Don't run around!
I'll beat you to death when we get back.
Hit him.
Hit him!
He's about to finish peeing!
Hurry up!
Hit him!
What the hell?
Step on the gas!
Handbrake! Handbrake!
Hit him!
Pay!
You have to pay for this car.
[Hygiene and Health]
You have to pay for it!
Little bastard.
Can you talk like this?
Can you talk?
Yes.
What happened to the car?
[Hygiene and Health]
Did it move by itself?
What do you mean?
Did I buy a Transformer?
Did it go save the earth by itself?
N-No, no, Mr. Li.
I... I really don't know what happened.
I just wanted to drive the car
forward a bit
to pick you up earlier.
I... I don't know what happened either.
I just heard someone yell in my ear.
I got startled, and then...
Mr. Li, I really didn't mean to hit you.
Really.
Who yelled at you?
I don't know what it was.
The car yelled at you?
No. I just heard it.
Was it Optimus Prime?
-I really... really don't know.
-The car yelled at you?
I know, I know.
I know what happened.
Gods and immortals,
drive away the vengeful spirits for me.
Drive away the vengeful spirits.
Vengeful spirits of the East, scatter!
Vengeful spirits of the West, begone!
Vengeful spirits of the South, perish!
Vengeful spirits of the North, depart!
Heavenly Soldiers, assemble as ordered!
Why hasn't it been driven away
after so long?
It's fiercer than the last one
you dealt with.
-Fiercer?
-Yeah.
Of course it's fiercer.
I almost couldn't handle it.
My goodness.
Scatter!
Here.
Here, drink it while it's hot.
Is... Is this thing... drinkable?
You should drink it quickly.
No, this... this...
What are you thinking? Just drink it.
Master told you to drink it,
so drink it.
Hurry up!
That's enough.
Oh my God.
That should do it.
Done?
Oh my God.
Look.
Master, Master.
What do you think possessed him?
I can't tell you.
It's a vengeful spirit.
I've temporarily hypnotized it.
But we can't say its name.
If we say the name,
it will wake up again.
To protect this man,
I've covered him with a big shield.
Now non-humans can't see him.
He's fine now.
He's been covered?
Yes.
Um, um...
How did this happen, Ms. Wan?
What has my family done recently?
Things like this happen every few days.
What did we provoke?
Born in the Year of the Monkey, right?
No wonder.
What were you two lifetimes ago?
You were a great general.
Your heroic spirit still lingers.
The ones coming to you
are all your former soldiers.
Why do they all come to you?
Because you are righteous and kind.
Why do they keep coming?
Because you didn't just lead
one or two soldiers.
You led thousands of them.
Think about it. Am I right?
How... How...
How can I suppress these...
Ms. Wan, thank you for your hard work.
Please accept this.
What are you doing?
-That's too much.
-No, no. Ms. Wan.
Let's fix this completely this time.
If no one comes to my husband again,
he'll be at ease.
Right?
Yes, it must be fixed completely.
Fix this completely. Yes.
Hurry. G-Give all the money to Master.
Don't be stingy.
G-Give all the money to Master.
Give all the money.
Nothing left. Th-That's all we have now.
-Of course. I'll fix this completely.
-That's all the money we have now.
Okay, I-I understand. How about this?
I'll light longevity lamps for you
in the Buddhist hall.
Okay?
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
-Thank you, Ms. Wan.
-Amitabha.
We... We
have been brought together by fate.
Hong,
I'm begging you.
Let's stop trying to kill him.
If you keep doing this,
I'll die before him sooner or later.
Really.
We'll stop.
I've thought about it.
We're not professionals at killing.
After everything we've done,
he didn't even get a scratch.
Killing
is a job for professionals.
Go to the Yuhong Square nightclub.
Find Dong
and ask him
to take care of Li Dewu.
Where did you get this money?
From the safe.
How did you know the code?
When Fatty Li gets drunk,
he spills everything.
Get it done quickly.
We can't let him find out
the money is missing.
What are you doing here?
Looking for...
Looking for Dong.
Why are you looking for him?
To talk business.
How much is this?
You think 50,000 yuan is enough
to get me to kill someone for you?
This...
This... This is the... the deposit.
Y-You'll get the other half
when the job's done.
Who do you want to kill?
The boss of Wenwu Lubricants,
Li Dewu.
Li Dewu?
The one who always goes
to Shasha Hair Salon to wash his hair?
I don't know him.
Someone else asked me to come.
Come on.
Aren't you his driver?
You're wearing sunglasses.
Are you going to play Erquan Yingyue?
What? You know me?
Not only do I know you,
I also know the car you drive.
Every day, you take him out to eat
and get his hair washed.
So stop pretending.
Go back and wait for news.
I'll let you know when it's done.
Aren't you going
to write a receipt or something?
When did you come in?
You came back to steal my money,
didn't you?
No.
I'll take this job.
He is my disease.
If he dies,
I'll be cured.
Either he dies
or I do.
Hit him!
Follow the direction of my soybeans.
Over there!
Over here! Over here!
Over here!
Over there.
Over here. Over here.
Over here!
Is this Li Dewu?
I'm from the Municipal Bureau.
And
I'm in charge of your husband's case.
When was the last time you saw Li Dewu?
Yesterday... morning.